[
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T02:59:52.631332",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "i went out so that made me happy"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:02:18.363331",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "i went out so that made me proud"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:06:57.272330",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "i am proud of myself"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:08:04.206956",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What\u2019s been on your mind lately?",
    "response": "nothing much just work"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:08:28.210928",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "proud of myself"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:08:36.491734",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "proud of myself"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:08:57.060709",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Something you're grateful for right now?",
    "response": "i am grateful for me"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:09:02.140512",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Something you're grateful for right now?",
    "response": "i am grateful for me"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:09:54.320205",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Something you're grateful for right now?",
    "response": "i am grateful for food"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:10:00.114237",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Something you're grateful for right now?",
    "response": "i am grateful for water"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:10:51.512530",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "i completed an app"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:14:37.310420",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "i went out so that made me happy"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:15:00.351863",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "found the loml"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:19:41.519131",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "i am grateful for me"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:19:52.521289",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "i am grateful for him"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:19:59.932837",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "my friends"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:26:06.321951",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "i am proud of me"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:26:12.017932",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "apple"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:27:28.160979",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "nothing much just work"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:27:34.743945",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "apple"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:28:13.635785",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Something you're grateful for right now?",
    "response": "banana"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:28:22.838716",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "me"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:31:15.339381",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "nothing much just work"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:32:06.112546",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "me"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:32:15.235913",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "won a tournament"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:32:21.403647",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What\u2019s been on your mind lately?",
    "response": "nothing"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:32:40.431658",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "i went out so that made me happy"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:32:46.128149",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "i am grateful for him"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:32:49.991015",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What\u2019s been on your mind lately?",
    "response": "nothing"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:33:59.323869",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "me"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:34:11.075621",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What\u2019s been on your mind lately?",
    "response": "nothing muuch"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:34:19.361819",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What\u2019s been on your mind lately?",
    "response": "kuch zyaada nahi"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:34:24.693198",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "won a tournament"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:34:42.094178",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Describe a recent small win.",
    "response": "game"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:35:09.648886",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What are you proud of this week?",
    "response": "my grades"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-20T03:35:15.983769",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd What made you smile today?",
    "response": "food <3"
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "2025-04-21T11:25:29.352184",
    "prompt": "\ud83d\udcdd Something you're grateful for right now?",
    "response": "hi"
  }
]